<resources>
    
    <string name="text_welcome1_button_1">Log in with Gold</string>

    <string name="text_welcome_button_1">Tourists try</string>
    <string name="text_welcome_button_2">log in</string>
    <string name="text_welcome_button_3">registered</string>
    
    <string name="text_pay_1">Gold Autumn Pay</string>
    <string name="text_pay_2">Name of commodity：</string>
    <string name="text_pay_3">Amount：</string>
    <string name="text_pay_4">Choice of payment</string>
    <string name="text_pay_5">Continue</string>
    <string name="text_pay_6">Google play</string>
    <string name="text_pay_8">Pay for success</string>
    <string name="text_pay_9">Pay as a result, confirmed</string>
    <string name="text_pay_10">PayPal</string>
    <string name="text_pay_12">unionpay</string>
    <string name="text_pay_14">Pay for failure</string>
    
    <string name="text_share_t">Share</string>
    
    <string name="text_paydata_1">Record</string>
    <string name="text_paydata_2">Name:</string>
    <string name="text_paydata_3">Amount:</string>
    <string name="text_paydata_4">To view</string>
    <string name="text_paydata_5">You also do not buy any goods</string>
    
    <string name="text_login_forgotpassword">Forgot account?</string>
    <string name="text_login_forgotpassword_title">Find Your Account</string>
    <string name="text_login_forgotpassword_title1">Reset Your Password</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_2">可以通过以下方式找回密码</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_3">Through the phone back</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_4">Continue</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_5">Input Account</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_6">Enter code:</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_7">enter code</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_8">Send enter</string>
    <string name="text_change_1">Account:</string>
    <string name="text_change_2">Reset Your Password</string>
    <string name="text_change_3">Old:</string>
    <string name="text_change_4">new:</string>
    <string name="text_change_5">again:</string>
    <string name="text_change_6">Old Password</string>
    <string name="text_change_7">New Password</string>
    <string name="text_change_8">Password again</string>
    <string name="text_bind_1">Binding phone</string>
    <string name="text_bind_2">Send enter</string>
    <string name="text_bind_3">Phone:</string>
    <string name="text_bind_4">Phone number</string>
    <string name="text_bind_5">Enter code:</string>
    <string name="text_bind_6">Binding</string>
    <string name="text_bind_7">Failed to retrieve the current login account, please login procedure</string>
    <string name="text_usercenter">User center</string>
    <string name="text_upgrade">upgrade</string>
    <string name="text_upgrade_1">Tourists:</string>
    <string name="text_user_1">Account:</string>
    <string name="text_user_2">Phone:</string>
    <string name="text_user_3">（unbounded）</string>
    <string name="text_user_4">Binding</string>
    <string name="text_user_6">Change password</string>
    <string name="text_user_8">Retrieve password</string>
    <string name="text_user_10">Logout</string>

    <string name="login_button_1">Enter</string>
    <string name="login_text_1">Account:</string>
    <string name="login_text_2">Password:</string>
    <string name="login_text_3">Password:</string>
    <string name="login_edit_1">Account/Phone</string>
    <string name="login_edit_2">password</string>
    <string name="registered_edit">Password again</string>
    <string name="username_or_pws_nil">The user name and password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="username_nil">User name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="msg_or_pws_nil">Authentication code and password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="pws_or_newpws_nil">The old password and new password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="phone_nil">Phone number is 11 Numbers and cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="msg_nil">Please enter the verification code</string>
    <string name="password_isfail">Two do not match the password input, please input again</string>
    <string name="network_error">Please check the network status and try again.</string>
    <string name="dialog_del">Confirm Delete？</string>
    <string name="dialog_del_float">Sure you want to hide the suspend button?After the restart the game will open again.</string>
    <string name="dialog_del_no">cancel</string>
    <string name="dialog_del_yes">delete</string>
    <string name="dialog_del_yes_1">hidden</string>
    <string name="dialog_exit_back">Return to the game</string>
    <string name="dialog_exit_yes">Quit</string>
    <string name="login_ing">In the login</string>
    <string name="authmethod_ing">In the validation</string>
    <string name="sendmessage_ing">Send in the</string>
    <string name="resetPassword_ing">In the change password</string>
    <string name="bindPhone_ing">Binding in the mobile phone</string>
    <string name="visitorUpdate_ing">Binding in the mobile phone</string>
    <string name="registered_ing">In the register</string>
    <string name="pay_ing">Generated in order</string>
    <string name="login_success">Login success</string>
    <string name="registered_success">Registered success</string>
    <string name="login_fail_username">Account must be used 5-20 digits or letters</string>
    <string name="login_fail_password">Password must use 6-20 digits or letters</string>
    <string name="msg_fail">Enter code is 6 digits</string>
    <string name="registered_title">Registration</string>
    <string name="registered_button_text">Registration</string>
    <string name="registered_text_1">Agreed</string>
    <string name="registered_text_2">《Gold User agreement》</string>
    <string name="protocol_title">Gold User agreement</string>
    <string name="protocol_tv1">Service code of conduct</string>
    <string name="protocol_button_tv1">The rules of the service</string>
    <string name="protocol_button_tv2">GM regulations</string>
    <string name="protocol_button_tv3">User agreement</string>
    <string name="protocol_button_tv4">Violation Handling</string>
    <string name="protocol_button_tv5">Game Announcement</string>
    <string name="float_button_1">account</string>
    <string name="float_button_2">affiche</string>
    <string name="float_button_3">hidden</string>
    <string name="float_button_4">BBS</string>
    <string name="notice_title">User agreement</string>
    <string name="notice">Kinsho game network technology (Shanghai) Co. Ltd. pass user service agreement \n1. \n3.4.4 special note if the gold business game suspected stolen account, has the right to terminate the membership of the right to use the account. \n3.4.5 if the user\'s own reasons, resulting in accounts, passwords are illegal use of others, the gold business game will not be responsible for processing. The user\'s own reasons include, but are not limited to: to disclose to the third party accounts and passwords and all registration information; many people share the same account; installation of illegal or unknown procedures, etc.. The service content \n4. ownership \n4.1 gold dealers are included in the game and / or relates to all the work and the data (including but not limited to any subtitles, computer code, subject, object, the role of the game, the game character name, story, dialogue, popular language, game concept, art, animation, sound, music, audio-visual effects, operation methods, documents, records, copies of chat online game character information, game client and server software etc.), the copyright and patent, trademark, trade secret and other intellectual property rights, are taking the game gold or authorized gold business game using the legitimate rights of all people. Unless authorized in advance by taking gold game or the rights of any person shall be allowed to use in any form, otherwise the game may terminate immediately to the gold business Users to provide products and services, and shall be held accountable for their legal liability, compensation for all losses. \n4.2 is not authorized by the gold business game, no one is allowed to copy, decompile, disassemble (de-compile) (disassemble) any functions or procedures, not to reverse engineer any function and / or program (reverse engineering). \n4.3 user hereby agree and confirm the user account data, and all other relevant information, including personal information, account users in the game characters and virtual items (unless otherwise agreed, the terms of "virtual goods" includes the game virtual currency, props, equipment, materials, etc.) are owned by the gold business game all. \n5 service, suspension and termination of \n5.1 service termination \n users hereby agree and confirm that it has one of the following acts, the gold business game has the right to suspend part or all of the services provided for the user, do freezing treatment on the account: \n5.1.1 provides false registration identity information; \ \ n5.1.2 to implement the illegal behavior of this Agreement; \n5.1.3 implementation of the third party damage user rights or interests; the implementation of \n5.1.4 5.1.1 and 5.1.2 in the user behavior, taking gold game has the right to suspend part or all of the services provided for the user\'s game in gold; measures taken to suspend, will inform the user during the suspension, during the suspension should be reasonable, after the expiration of the period of suspension taking the game, gold should restore service to users in a timely manner. However, if the default state of the user remains at the end of the period of suspension, the dealer game has the right to extend the period of suspension of service. \n5.1.5 gold business game based on the user to implement 5.1.1 and 5.1.2 behavior, to take measures to stop the service, should bear the corresponding burden of proof. The \n5.2 service terminated \n users agreed to temporarily implement the following behavior, gold dealers have the right to terminate the game to provide services for the users, delete the account: \n5.2.1 release illegal information; \n\n5.2.2 serious violation of social morality and other violations of the law prohibited provisions of the act; \n5.2.3 through illegal means, or improper means other unfair means the use of gold business services or to participate in the gold business game game; \n5.2.4 game normally interference gold dealers to provide products and services, including but not limited to: attack, invade Jin Shang game website server, game server client program or web server overload; \n5.2.5 crack, modified gold taking the game client; hinder the fairness of the game or auxiliary tool for \n5.2.6 production, publishing, dissemination and use in any form Order (plug-in); \n5.2.7 application vulnerabilities and error (Bug) gamebreaking normal or spread the vulnerability or error (Bug); \n5.2.8 did not use the gold business game provides service for 180 consecutive days (calculated from the user\'s last service date), from the 180th day of the day 24 when taking the game gold, have the right to take measures to stop the users continue to use the service, delete the user account, including but not limited to the registration information, class information and character information, goods information and all related and registered account information, and do not need to delete any losses brought by the account for the \n5.2.9 implementation; other unreasonably interfere or obstruct others using gold business game service or damage the interests of users and provide other rights behavior; \n5.2.10 gold to implement 5.2.1 and 5.2.2 game based on user behavior, take Termination of service measures, should bear the corresponding burden of proof. \n5.3 in order to maintain and ensure the fairness of the user\'s service game gold, found abnormal user data in the gold business game, regardless of whether the user has fault of the abnormal data is generated if, taking gold game entitled under this Agreement and not regularly publish service announcements, take corresponding measures, including but not limited to the account of freezing, suspension, termination, delete the user; this commitment gold dealers have the right to make the game behavior, and promised not to the gold business game behavior requirements any form of compensation or refund. \n6, the user\'s obligation \n6.1 to provide services related to their own equipment (such as computers, modems and other devices connected to the Internet) and bear the costs (such as access to each other)</string>
    <string name="text_forgot_9">请输入您绑定的手机号</string>
    <string name="spinner_zh">中国</string>
    <string name="spinner_en">United States</string>
</resources>
